swap.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy policy – Swap.com Support

LAST UPDATED: 10 April, 2019

## SWAP.COM, INC. PRIVACY POLICY

### I. Introduction

Swap.com, Inc. (“we, “us) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to in it) applies to swap.com website (the “Site”) and mobile application (the “App”) (the Site and the App collectively the “Service”) and sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be handled by us. In this Privacy Policy, the term “personal data” means information that relates to an identified or identifiable natural person. This Privacy Policy tells you about the ways in which we protect your privacy and personal data we process about you.

We wish to remind you that this Privacy Policy applies to personal data that we process when you use the Service. It does not apply to any links to third parties’ websites and/or services, such as third-party applications, that you may encounter when you use the Service. We encourage you to carefully familiarize yourself with privacy policies applicable to any websites and/or services operated by third parties. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties.

### II. Information We May Collect From You

(i) Data You Provide to the Service

We may collect the following information from our registered (signed up) users (“Registered Users”) that may, in certain circumstances, constitute personal data:

  * Password;
  * Name;
  * E-mail address;
  * Phone number;
  * Address;
  * Shopping preferences;
  * Date of birth;
  * Country of origin;
  * Gender; and
  * Paypal account email address.

If you use a third party service, such as Facebook Connect, for signing into the Service, we may collect personal data, such as your user ID, name, and e-mail address, that are available in accordance with the terms of service and the privacy settings of the third party service you use for signing into the Service. You may control the types of personal data available in the public profile of such third party services by adjusting the privacy settings available therein. Moreover, if you contact us, a record of this correspondence may be kept.

(ii) Data Collected Automatically

Certain information on the Service is collected automatically by means of various software tools. We have a legitimate interest in using such information to assist in log-in, systems administration purposes, information security and abuse prevention and detection, to track user trends, and to analyze the effectiveness of the Service. Alone or in combination with other information, such automatically collected information may constitute personal data. Some of our service providers (described in Section III, below) may use cookies or other methods to gather information regarding your use of the Service. Such third parties may use these cookies or other tracking methods for their own purposes by relating information about your use of the Service with any of personal data about you that they may have. The use of such information by a third party depends on the privacy policy of that third party. The Service may automatically collect the following information from:

  * **The logging technology used in the Service automatically collects the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the Service. We also collect the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the device you use to access the Service, information about the operating system of your device, as well as the name of your Internet service provider.**
  * We may place a “cookie” on the hard drive of the device that you use to access the Service. Cookies are text files that are saved on the hard drive of your device by means of your browser, enabling us to recognize your browser for purposes such as saving your preferences and directing relevant content to you. Most of the currently available browsers give you the option of managing cookies by, for example, disabling them entirely, accepting them individually, and deleting saved cookies from your hard drive. We would like to remind you that if you completely disable cookies on your browser, you might not be able to use some features of the Service.
  * From time-to-time, we may engage third parties to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information from individuals who visit the Site. We sometimes use cookies delivered by third parties to track the performance of our advertisements. For example, these cookies remember which browsers have visited the Site. By way of example, as you browse the Site, advertising cookies may be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our advertising partners then enable us to present you with retargeted advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with our Site. To learn more about these and other advertising networks and their opt out instructions, click [here.](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/)
  * Google Analytics is an element of the Service. By using cookies, Google Analytics collects and stores data such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the website, the Internet Protocol address, and the type of operating system used in the devices used to access the Service. By using a [browser plugin](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin/) provided by Google, you can opt out of Google Analytics.

Moreover, details of transactions you carry out through the Service, the fulfillment of your orders, details of your visits to the Site and the App including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data may also be collected.

### III. How We Disclose Data

We do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose the personal data relating to our Registered Users to third parties unless otherwise stated below.

The personal data collected in the Service may be disclosed in the following manner:

a) Personal data you provide to the Service:

We may disclose personal data you provide to the Service with the following categories of third parties:

  * To service providers, such as payment processors and data storage service providers, which enable us to provide the Service to you;
  * To public authorities, such as law enforcement, if we are legally required to so or if we need to protect our rights or the rights of third parties; and
  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates; or a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Service and their advisors in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, or the sale of substantially all of our stock and/or assets or other corporate reorganization, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

b) Data collected automatically:

The data collected automatically in the Service may be disclosed to the following categories of third parties:

  * To service providers, such as data analysis and advertising technology companies;
  * To public authorities, such as law enforcement, if we are legally required to do so or if we need to protect our rights or the rights of third parties; and
  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates; or a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Service and their advisors in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, or the sale of substantially all of our stock and/or assets or other corporate reorganization, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Moreover, we may disclose information to third parties in an aggregate format that does not constitute personal data and does not allow the identification of individual Registered Users.

### IV. Your Rights

You have the following rights with respect to the personal data we hold about you:

  * The right to know what data we hold about you: If you would like to know what personal data we hold about you, please contact us at . We seek to swiftly respond to your inquiry. We may charge a small processing fee if less than twelve (12) months has passed since your last inquiry relating to personal data we hold about you.
  * The right to have incomplete, incorrect, outdated, or unnecessary personal data corrected, deleted, or updated. The easiest way to correct, delete, or update the personal data you have provided to the Service is to log in to the Service and enter the necessary changes in the account settings of the Service. If you have additional questions regarding the correction, deletion, or updating of the personal data we hold about you, please contact us at .
  * The right to opt out of receiving electronic direct marketing communications from us: All electronic direct marketing communications that you may receive from us, such as e-mail messages and SMS-messages, give you an option of not receiving such communications from us in the future. If you have any additional questions about electronic direct marketing received from us, please contact us at .
  * Depending on where you live, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority or other regulatory agency if you believe that we have violated any of the rights concerning personal data about you.  We encourage you to first reach out to us at  so we have an opportunity to address your concerns directly before you do so.

### V. Data Security

All information you provide to us is stored on our or our hosting providers' secure servers. Please note that the Service is hosted in cloud servers in the US, in European Union or in another location. Any payment transactions will be encrypted. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of this site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. Please do not share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect personal data about you, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Service; any transmission is at your own risk.

### VI. Children’s Privacy

This Service is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal data from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal data without their consent, he or she should contact us at . If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal data, we will delete such information from our files.

### VII. Changes to the Privacy Policy

From time to time we may change this Privacy Policy. You can tell when changes have been made to the Privacy Policy by referring to the “Last Updated” legend on top of this page. If we materially change the ways in which we use and disclose personal data, we will post a notice in the Service and send an e-mail to our registered (signed up) users. Your continued use of the Service following any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of any such changes made.

### VIII. Questions or Concerns?

Should you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, your privacy as it relates to the use of the Service, or the protection of the personal data we hold about you, please contact us via e-mail at  or by mail at Swap.com Inc., 2501 Internationale Pkwy, Suite 100  
Woodridge, IL 60517. We seek to swiftly resolve any concerns you may have.
